<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="AppName">Petus</string>

	<!-- Screen titles -->
	<string name="ZooScreenTitle">Home</string>
	<string name="CemeteryScreenTitle">Cemetery</string>
	<string name="WeatherScreenTitle">Weather</string>
	<string name="ProfileScreenTitle">Profile</string>
	<string name="QuestsScreenTitle">Quests</string>

	<!-- User profile -->
	<string name="ProfileScreenLanguagesLabel">Languages</string>
	<string name="ProfileScreenInventoryLabel">Inventory</string>
	<string name="ProfileScreenAbilitiesLabel">Abilities</string>
	<string name="LanguageKnowledgeTitleCatus">Catus language</string>
	<string name="LanguageKnowledgeTitleDogus">Dogus language</string>
	<string name="LanguageKnowledgeTitleFrogus">Frogus language</string>
	<string name="LanguageKnowledgeTitleBober">Bober language</string>
	<string name="LanguageKnowledgeTitleFractal">Fractal language</string>
	<string name="LanguageKnowledgeTitleDragon">Dragon language</string>
	<string name="ZooSizeTitle">Home size</string>
	<string name="ProfileScreenMiscLabel">Misc</string>
	<string name="CanPetsDieOfOldAge">Can pets die of old age?</string>

	<!-- Zoo screen -->
	<string name="CreatePetButtonTitle">Create new pet</string>

	<!-- Pet details -->
	<string name="WillHatchSoon">Will hatch soon…</string>
	<string name="ButtonTitleFeed">Feed</string>
	<string name="ButtonTitlePlay">Play</string>
	<string name="ButtonTitleHeal">Heal</string>
	<string name="ButtonTitlePoop">Clean</string>
	<string name="ButtonTitleWakeUp">Wake up</string>
	<string name="ButtonTitleBury">Bury</string>
	<string name="ButtonTitleSpeak">Speak</string>
	<string name="ButtonTitleResurrect">Resurrect</string>
	<string name="ButtonTitleForget">Forget</string>

	<!-- Pet creation screen -->
	<string name="PetCreationScreenSelectPetType">Select pet type</string>
	<string name="PetCreationScreenEnterPetName">Enter pet name:</string>
	<string name="PetCreationScreenEnterPetNameHint">Pet name</string>
	<string name="PetCreationScreenPetTypeDogus">dogus</string>
	<string name="PetCreationScreenPetTypeCatus">catus</string>
	<string name="PetCreationScreenPetTypeFrogus">frogus</string>
	<string name="PetCreationScreenPetTypeBober">bober</string>
	<string name="PetCreationScreenPetTypeFractal">fractal</string>
	<string name="PetCreationScreenPetTypeDragon">dragon</string>
	<string name="PetCreationScreenButtonTemplate">Create %s %s</string>
	<string name="PetCreationScreenButtonTemplateFractal">Imagine fractal %s</string>

	<!-- Pet descriptions -->
	<string name="PetTypeDescriptionCatus">Catus: sleeps 2 hours, awake for 1 hour. Likes warm sunny days. Likes small wind.</string>
	<string name="PetTypeDescriptionDogus">Dogus: sleeps 1 hour, awake for 2 hours. Likes warm sunny days. Likes medium wind.</string>
	<string name="PetTypeDescriptionFrogus">Frogus: sleeps 1.5 hours, awake for 1.5 hours. Likes cold cloudy days. Does not like wind.</string>
	<string name="PetTypeDescriptionBober">Bober: sleeps 1 hours, awake for 2 hours. Likes warm sunny days. Does not like wind.</string>
	<string name="PetTypeDescriptionFractal">Fractal: sleeps 1.5 hours, awake for 1.5 hours. Does not care about weather since it is just an idea.</string>
	<string name="PetTypeDescriptionDragon">Dragon: sleeps 1.5 hours, awake for 1.5 hours. Different types of dragons like different weather</string>

	<!-- Item names -->
	<string name="Necronomicon">Necronomicon</string>
	<string name="PieceOfCloth">Piece of cloth</string>
	<string name="MysteriousBook">Mysterious book</string>
	<string name="Fish">Fish</string>
	<string name="FrogusEgg">Frogus egg</string>
	<string name="DogusEgg">Dogus egg</string>
	<string name="CatusEgg">Catus egg</string>
	<string name="BoberEgg">Bober egg</string>
	<string name="Basket">Wicker basket</string>
	<string name="DragonEgg">Dragon egg</string>
	<string name="TwoMeterRuler">2 meter stick</string>
	<string name="TenCentimeterRuler">10 centimeter stick</string>
	<string name="MathBook">What Is Mathematics?</string>
	<string name="MemoryOfMage">Memory of the Magician</string>
	<string name="MemoryOfWarrior">Memory of the Warrior</string>
	<string name="MemoryOfBard">Memory of the Bard</string>
	<string name="MemoryOfSmith">Memory of the Smith</string>
	<string name="CurseOfMage">Curse of the Mage</string>
	<string name="CurseOfWarrior">Curse of the Warrior</string>
	<string name="CurseOfBard">Curse of the Bard</string>
	<string name="CurseOfSmith">Curse of the Smith</string>
	<string name="InventoryItemPattern">%s (x%d)</string>

	<!-- Item descriptions -->
	<string name="ItemDescNecronomicon">The Necronomicon is a grimoire that contains forbidden knowledge, occult rituals, and descriptions of cosmic entities like Cthulhu and the Great Old Ones. It is a dangerous book that drives readers to madness.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescPieceOfCloth">Piece of cloth found at the crime scene.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescMysteriousBook">Mysterious book found at a ritual site.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescFish">Not a very smart fish caught at the pond.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescFrogusEgg">Found by Catus at the pond. Allows the spawning of new Froguses.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescDogusEgg">It has been with me for as long as I can remember.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescCatusEgg">It has been with me for as long as I can remember.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescBoberEgg">Provided to us by the bobers community to support their population.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescDragonEgg">Rescued from the hands of the powerful necromancer Valherris, it allows one to raise dragons.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescBasket">Beautiful and reliable basket for storing eggs (with a lid).</string>
	<string name="ItemDescTwoMeterRuler">A huge ruler, taller than me.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescTenCentimeterRuler">A very small ruler, fits in your pocket.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescMathBook">What Is Mathematics? - book by Herbert Robbins and Richard Courant</string>
	<string name="ItemDescMemoryOfMage">In the kingdom, the legendary mage’s name is not spoken aloud in haste. He was inscribed in the Book of Royal Archmages not with gold ink, but with black — the mark of those who gave their lives, leaving behind no school, disciples, or heirs, to save the world itself.\n\nIn the mage towers, students begin their training with the same legend. They are told of the Protector without followers — a mage who founded no order, wrote no treatises, and sought no recognition, but in his hour of need stood between the living and death.\n\nBefore difficult spells, young mages place their hand momentarily on the cold stone of the wall and whisper his name — not as a prayer, but as a reminder: true magic serves not glory, but choice.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescMemoryOfWarrior">The legendary warrior’s sacrifice is spoken of simply in the kingdom, without lofty words.\n\nHis sword was returned to its source — the family crypt — and it wasn’t the priests or military leaders who insisted on this, but the common people.\n\nPeasants, merchants, and artisans leave small tokens of gratitude at the crypt entrance: a broken horseshoe, a piece of leather, a bundle of grain. No one calls it a tradition — it’s simply done when they remember.\nThey say he fought not for victory, but so that others would have time to escape, and therefore his sword shouldn’t be visible — it should rest.\n\nSometimes, on rainy days, a lantern is lit near the crypt. Not in honor of the hero, but so that the path home will always be illuminated, even if you never return.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescMemoryOfBard">The memory of the legendary bard lives in the kingdom not in stone or in books, but in voices.\nHis song has long since lost its words — everyone sings it in their own way, humming only fragments of a melody that cannot be captured in its entirety. But that’s how it’s passed on: not precisely, but vividly.\n\nChildren hum it as they play on the thresholds of houses, unaware of its origin. Travelers quietly pick it up on the road when the evening grows too long. No one calls it the memory of a hero — it’s simply a song that comes to them.\n\nAnd on clear nights, when the moon hangs low, some swear the wind suddenly begins to sound smoother and warmer. And if you listen closely, it seems as if someone is singing nearby — not for glory or reward, but so that the road doesn’t seem empty.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescMemoryOfSmith">The memory of the legendary blacksmith doesn’t resound loudly in the kingdom — it weighs heavily.\nHis hammer was returned to the forge of his hometown and hung by the hearth where he once worked. It’s no longer used to forge weapons, but it’s never removed: the fire in that forge has never gone out for a single night since.\n\nA monument was erected at the capital’s gates — a stone anvil, crude and simple. It bears no names or inscriptions: everyone knows to whom it’s dedicated. On the opening day, the dwarves of the Ash Caves stood in a circle and silently struck the ground with their hammers. No songs, no speeches — only a dull, heavy sound that shook the stones.\n\nSince then, they say: if the city gates suddenly become quieter than usual, it means someone has stopped at the anvil and remembered the one who once stayed so others could leave.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescCurseOfMage">Few know that the mage’s curse began in the Misty Gorge. One of the illusions, not completely dispelled, touched his face — and from then on, half of his features seemed to have a life of their own: reflected in glass incorrectly, whispering other people’s thoughts, remembering things that never happened.\n\nOver time, madness slowly began to consume him from within. Spells became increasingly difficult, sleep brought only fog, and his own reflection inspired fear. He tried to fight, sought healing, but realized that some distortions could not be reversed.\n\nOne day, he left alone, leaving no farewells. He was last seen at the edge of the Misty Gorge, where illusions never completely dissipate.\nThey say that now, among the shadows, one can discern a figure with a half-familiar face — it does not attack or call, only stares, as if still trying to remember who it was.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescCurseOfWarrior">The warrior’s curse was born not of magic, but of a choice denied.\nAt Stone Pass, he was prevented from confronting the giant — and this decision, made out of caution, left a rift deeper than any wound.\n\nHonor, unrequited, began to rot. He left alone, without words or witnesses, to reclaim what he considered rightfully his.\n\nBut when he returned to the pass, he was already broken: doubt dulled his hand, fatigue weighed his steps, and rage proved weaker than stone.\n\nHe didn’t last five minutes.\n\nNow the giant wears his cloak, draped over his shoulder like a warm cloth. He doesn’t know it’s a trophy, doesn’t understand its significance — and in this final humiliation, the warrior’s honor dissolved completely, becoming nothing more than the wind on the pass.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescCurseOfBard">The bard’s curse began in the Forest of Singing Winds, where he once dared to respond to the songs of the dryads. They managed to break through further, but the forest did not completely release him — part of the melody wove itself into his voice, leaving an alien rhythm within him.\n\nOver time, the songs ceased to be quiet. They came in his dreams, interrupted his thoughts, compelled him to sing even when he was silent. His music became strange: it contained a melancholy that made the listeners’ hearts clench, and a call that made them want to go — not knowing where.\n\nHe resisted to the last, but one day he realized he could no longer distinguish his own desires from those whispered by the forest. On a windless night, he left his house and walked into the thicket, following the voices that now sounded like a sentence.\n\nSince then, a wordless song is sometimes heard in the Forest of Singing Winds — uneven, broken. And those who recognize the human voice in it try to leave quickly: they say the forest sings through the one who once tried to answer it.</string>
	<string name="ItemDescCurseOfSmith">The blacksmith’s curse began in the Ash Caves, when he found red crystals, warm as life, amid the slag and rusty machinery. He mistook them for a rare ore and began studying them, testing their sound and impact, without noticing how they began to respond to him.\n\nAt first, the crystals merely drove him mad — distorting time, making him hear meaningful words in the grinding of gears. Then they sprouted: scarlet veins appeared beneath his skin, his bones grew heavier, his movements slower but stronger.\n\nWhen he realized he could no longer distinguish his own will from the call of the earth, it was too late. He removed his hammer, left it at the entrance, and went deeper into the caves, where fire and stone never sleep.\nThey say that now in the Ash Caves, a mechanism that no one has ever set in motion sometimes moves, and in its rhythm one can hear the heavy breathing of one who has chosen to merge with the earth forever.</string>

	<!-- Meditation exercises -->
	<string name="MeditationExerciseBreathAwareness">Breath Awareness</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseBoxBreathing">Box Breathing</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseBodyScan">Body Scan</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseLovingKindnessPhrases">Loving-Kindness Phrases</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseCountingTheBreath">Counting the Breath</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseMantraRepetition">Mantra Repetition</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseWalkingMeditation">Walking Meditation</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseCandleGazing">Candle Gazing</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseNotingPractice">Noting Practice</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseFiveSensesAwareness">Five Senses Awareness</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseVisualization">Visualization</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseMountainMeditation">Mountain Meditation</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseSoundAwareness">Sound Awareness</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseTonglenExercise">Tonglen Exercise</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseGratitudeReflection">Gratitude Reflection</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseMindfulEating">Mindful Eating</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseProgressiveRelaxation">Progressive Relaxation</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseChakraFocusing">Chakra Focusing</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseSelfInquiryQuestions">Self-Inquiry Questions</string>
	<string name="MeditationExerciseSilentSitting">Silent Sitting</string>

	<!-- Abilities names -->
	<string name="Necromancy">Necromancy</string>
	<string name="Meditation">Meditation</string>

	<!-- Notifications -->
	<string name="NotificationInventoryItemAdded">%s added</string>
	<string name="NotificationInventoryItemRemoved">%s removed</string>

	<!-- Onboarding -->
	<string name="OnboardingHomeTitle">Home</string>
	<string name="OnboardingHomeMessage">Here you can see all your pets. Take good care of them!</string>
	<string name="OnboardingSatietyTitle">Satiety</string>
	<string name="OnboardingSatietyMessage">Each pet has 3 main stats: Satiety (green) - feed your pet when this stat is low.</string>
	<string name="OnboardingPsycheTitle">Psyche</string>
	<string name="OnboardingPsycheMessage">Psyche (blue) - it’s your animal’s mental health. Play with your pet to increase it and let your pet have a good UNINTERRUPTED nap. Your pet may not want to spend the time with you if you wake it up.</string>
	<string name="OnboardingHealthTitle">Health</string>
	<string name="OnboardingHealthMessage">Health (red) - it decreases if you pet’s satiety and psyche aren’t high enough. If it reaches zero, your pet will die.</string>
	<string name="OnboardingIllnessTitle">Illness</string>
	<string name="OnboardingIllnessMessage">Your pet might become ill. Ill pets are more needy. Their satiety and psyche decrease faster. You can heal an ill pet.</string>
	<string name="OnboardingCleanUpTitle">Clean up</string>
	<string name="OnboardingCleanUpMessage">Your pet will poop from time to time. Clean up after your pet to keep its psyche high.</string>
	<string name="OnboardingTalkTitle">Talk</string>
	<string name="OnboardingTalkMessage">You can talk to your pet in its own language, but it’s obviously not easy to talk to a pet. Play with your pets regularly to understand them better.</string>
	<string name="OnboardingAgeTitle">Age</string>
	<string name="OnboardingAgeMessage">Pets grow over time, from egg to adult. Their needs differ throughout their lifetime, so observe your pets carefully.</string>
	<string name="OnboardingGoodLuckTitle">Good luck!</string>
	<string name="OnboardingGoodLuckMessage">Take good care of your pets to keep them alive and happy! Good luck!</string>
	<string name="OnboardingSkipTitle">Skip</string>
	<string name="OnboardingPreviousTitle">Back</string>
	<string name="OnboardingNextTitle">Next</string>
	<string name="OnboardingLetsGoTitle">Let’s go!</string>
	<string name="OnboardingHowToButtonTitle">How to play?</string>

	<!-- History events -->
	<string name="HistoryEventPetCreated">Created</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetWakeUp">Wake up</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetForciblyWakeUp">Forcibly wake up</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetSleep">Fall asleep</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetGetIll">Get ill</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetGetHealed">Get healed</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetFeed">Been fed</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetPlay">Played with</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetDied">Died</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetCleanUp">Cleaned up</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetBecomeNewborn">Become newborn</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetBecomeTeen">Become teen</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetBecomeAdult">Become adult</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetBecomeOld">Become old</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetBuried">Buried</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetForgotten">Forgotten</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetResurrected">Resurrected</string>
	<string name="HistoryEventPetPoop">Pooped</string>

	<!-- Pet state description dialogs -->
	<string name="IAmSick">I am sick, do you have any medicine?</string>
	<string name="IAmSickLatin">Aeger sum, habesne medicamentum aliquod?</string>
	<string name="IAmSickPolish">Jestem chory. Czy masz jakieś lekarstwo?</string>
	<string name="IAmSickMath">[C = 2πr]</string>
	<string name="IAmHungry">I am hungry, give me some food.</string>
	<string name="IAmHungryLatin">Esurio, da mihi cibum.</string>
	<string name="IAmHungryPolish">Jestem głodny, daj mi trochę jedzenia.</string>
	<string name="IAmHungryMath">[sin^2(θ) + cos^2(θ) = 1]</string>
	<string name="IPooped">I pooped (it would be nice if you clean after me).</string>
	<string name="IPoopedLatin">Cacavi (gratum esset si post me lavares).</string>
	<string name="IPoopedPolish">Zrobiłem kupę (byłoby miło, gdybyś po mnie posprzątał).</string>
	<string name="IPoopedMath">[φ = (1 + √5) / 2]</string>
	<string name="IAmBored">I am bored, wanna play?</string>
	<string name="IAmBoredLatin">Taedet me, ludere vis?</string>
	<string name="IAmBoredPolish">Nudzę się, chcesz zagrać?</string>
	<string name="IAmBoredMath">[F - E + V = 2]</string>
	<string name="IAmStillAngryAfterForceWakeUp">I am still not happy that you woke me up for no reason!</string>
	<string name="IAmStillAngryAfterForceWakeUpLatin">Adhuc non gaudeo te me sine causa excitasse!</string>
	<string name="IAmStillAngryAfterForceWakeUpPolish">Nadal nie jestem zadowolony, że mnie obudziłeś bez powodu!</string>
	<string name="IAmStillAngryAfterForceWakeUpMath">[(-b ± √(b^2 - 4ac)) / 2a]</string>
	<string name="IAmHalfHp">I do not feel so good, need some rest.</string>
	<string name="IAmHalfHpLatin">Non tam bene me habeo, requie mihi opus est.</string>
	<string name="IAmHalfHpPolish">Nie czuję się najlepiej, muszę odpocząć.</string>
	<string name="IAmHalfHpMath">[a^2 + b^2 = c^2]</string>
	<string name="IAmGood">I am fine.</string>
	<string name="IAmGoodLatin">Bene sum.</string>
	<string name="IAmGoodPolish">Mam się dobrze.</string>
	<string name="IAmGoodMath">[e^(iπ) + 1 = 0]</string>
	<string name="IWillDie">As I am old, within the next five minutes I will die with a probability of %1$.3f%%.</string>
	<string name="IWillDieLatin">Quoniam senex sum, intra proximos quinque minutos cum probabilitate %1$.3f%% moriar.</string>
	<string name="IWillDiePolish">Ponieważ jestem już stary, w ciągu najbliższych pięciu minut umrę z prawdopodobieństwem %.3f%%.</string>

	<!-- Quests reset -->
	<string name="QuestResetAnswer0">I want to reset a specific quest to the beginning.</string>
	<string name="QuestResetDialog0">Q = ?</string>
	<string name="QuestResetAnswer1">I changed my mind, thank you</string>
	<string name="QuestResetDialog1">Q → ∅</string>

	<!-- Dialogs -->
	<string name="WhatIsGoingOnWithYou">What is going on with you?</string>
	<string name="WhatIsGoingOnWithYouLatin">Quid tecum agitur?</string>
	<string name="WhatIsGoingOnWithYouPolish">Jak się masz?</string>
	<string name="WhatIsGoingOnWithYouMathMandelbrot">1. c, z ∈ ℂ\n2. z ↦ z^2 + c\n3. ∀ c : z[0] = 0, n → ∞, |z[n]| ↛ ∞</string>
	<string name="WhatIsGoingOnWithYouMathGosper">1. ∠ 60°\n2. + := +60°\n3. — := -60°\n4. A\n5. A ↦ A — B — — B + A + + A A + B —\n6. B ↦ + A — B B — — B — A + + A + B</string>
	<string name="WhatIsGoingOnWithYouMathKoch">1. ∠ 60°\n2. + := +60°\n3. — := -60°\n4. F\n5. F ↦ F + F — — F + F</string>
	<string name="WhatIsGoingOnWithYouMathSponge">1. M := ∩{n∈ℕ} M[n]\n2. M[n+1] := { (x,y,z) ∈ ℝ^3 : ∃i,j,k ∈ {0,1,2} (3x - i, 3y - j, 3z - k) ∈ M[n], ¬((i=1 ∧ j=1) ∨ (i=1 ∧ k=1) ∨ (j=1 ∧ k=1)) }</string>
	<string name="BeenBetter">Been better.</string>
	<string name="IAmOkayHowAreYou">I am fine, how are you?</string>
	<string name="IShouldGo">I should go.</string>
	<string name="SeeYa">See ya.</string>
	<string name="ByeBye">Bye bye.</string>
	<string name="Sure">Sure</string>
	<string name="Ok">Ok</string>
	<string name="AllRight">All right</string>
	<string name="Excellent">Excellent!</string>
	<string name="Ellipsis">...</string>
	<string name="Thanks">Thanks</string>
	<string name="Use">Use</string>
	<string name="Destroy">Destroy</string>
	<string name="NecronomiconStage3AnswerOption0">Do you know anything about the dug grave?</string>
	<string name="NecronomiconStage3CommonDialog">Nope, do not know anything</string>
	<string name="NecronomiconStage3DogDialog">I do not know anything but we could investigate, bring me something from there.</string>
	<string name="NecronomiconStage3DogDialogAnswerOption0">Ok, I will see what I can find</string>
	<string name="NecronomiconStage5AnswerOption0">Look what I have found near the grave</string>
	<string name="NecronomiconStage5DogDialog">Hmm, interesting, let me see where it will lead me…</string>
	<string name="NecronomiconStage6AnswerOption0">Have you found anything?</string>
	<string name="NecronomiconStage6DogDialog">No, not yet, but I am searching.</string>
	<string name="NecronomiconStage7DogDialog0">Look, I have found this strange book on ritual site. Take it.</string>
	<string name="NecronomiconStage7AnswerOption0">Thanks, do you know who can help me with it?</string>
	<string name="NecronomiconStage7DogDialog1">Try to ask catus they usually more experienced in wisdom stuff, the older the better.</string>
	<string name="NecronomiconStage7DogDialog2">One more thing, at the same ritual site I have found the body of the lost pet. Poor guy. Do not worry I will return him back to his grave.</string>
	<string name="NecronomiconStage8AnswerOption0">[Show the book] Do you know anything about this book?</string>
	<string name="NecronomiconStage8Dialog0">What is this? I can sense some magic but I am not sure…</string>
	<string name="NecronomiconStage8Dialog1">Ahh, yes, I know what it is. This is Necronomicon. Very dangerous stuff, I recommend to destroy it right away, nothing good will come from it. However I can also teach you how to use it. Your choice. So do you want to use it or destroy it?</string>
	<string name="ObtainFrogusStage1Answer0">Hey buddy, I have noticed you barely touch your food, what is going on?</string>
	<string name="ObtainFrogusStage1Dialog0">Yeah, you know what, I think I want some fish, could you catch me some? There is a lake nearby I think you can try there.</string>
	<string name="ObtainFrogusStage1Answer1">All right, let us see what I can do. I think I will come up with something on next day.</string>
	<string name="ObtainFrogusStage3Answer0">Oi mate, here is fish you have asked for. From very same lake you described.</string>
	<string name="ObtainFrogusStage3Dialog0">Cheers mate, that is what I am talking about! Real fresh fish, el belissimo! Now I know this lake is good, think I will spend some time there by myself. Thanks again!</string>
	<string name="ObtainFrogusStage3Answer1">No problem!</string>
	<string name="ObtainFrogusStage5Answer0">Hey, what is that you are playing with?</string>
	<string name="ObtainFrogusStage5Dialog0">Ah, found it on the lake. Round and rolling! Also smells like slime but it is okay. Here, take it, I am done playing with it.</string>
	<string name="ObtainFrogusStage5Answer1">Thank you, I think I know what to do with it.</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage2Answer0">Hey, do you know where all the eggs went?</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage2Dialog0">Wow! I do not know anything about this, but I can look for it, ask me tomorrow, maybe I will find something.</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage2Dialog1">I do not know anything and, honestly, I do not care.</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage2Answer1">Thank you, I will come see you tomorrow!</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage3Answer0">Well, did you find anything?</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage3Dialog0">Nope, still looking.</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage4Dialog0">Aha, I found all the eggs, well, you made me run! I suspect that they just rolled away or maybe the wind blew them away, I put them back in place, now they definitely will not roll away.</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage6Answer0">The eggs are missing again, do you know anything about it?</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage6Dialog0">What, again? Oh my! Okay, I will look again, but after I find it, you better come up with something so that this does not happen again.</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage6Dialog1">Ahahahahahahahaha! Seriously? Well, screw them.</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage8Dialog0">Here they are, finally. Listen, I do not want to run around looking for the missing eggs again if something else happens to them. Ask someone else, maybe they can help, we need to solve this problem somehow.</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage8Answer0">Okay, I will ask around.</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage9Answer0">Maybe you know what to do with these constantly rolling eggs?</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage9Dialog0">Hmm, I do not know how to help you with this, but I think I know someone who knows what to do. My friends from the pond, handy guys. I will ask them, come see me tomorrow.</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage9Dialog1">I told you to ask someone else, do we all look the same to you?</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage9Dialog2">Well, do I look like someone who can control the wind?</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage10Answer0">Well, have you heard from your friends?</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage10Dialog0">They said they would do everything in the best possible way, wait a little longer.</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage11Dialog0">Yes! Look what they just sent us - a beautiful, reliable basket for storing eggs (with a lid). And along with the basket they sent a Bober egg - lucky!</string>
	<string name="ObtainBoberStage11Answer0">Truly a stroke of luck! I will have to try and hatch one or two.</string>
	<string name="ObtainFractalStage1Answer0">I see you have been thinking about something a lot lately, is everything okay?</string>
	<string name="ObtainFractalStage1Dialog0">Yes, everything is fine, I am thinking about one interesting task and want to test it in practice, but I have paws. Will you help me?</string>
	<string name="ObtainFractalStage1Dialog1">Thank you! Then take this two-meter stick and go measure the length of the shoreline of our pond. I am very interested in how much you measure.</string>
	<string name="ObtainFractalStage1Answer1">It will take me one day, I will report the results tomorrow.</string>
	<string name="ObtainFractalStage3Answer0">Hi, I measured the length of the coast - it was 4.76 kilometers, what is next?</string>
	<string name="ObtainFractalStage3Dialog0">Very good, very good. Let us write it down - 4.76 kilometers. Now take this smaller ruler and do the same.</string>
	<string name="ObtainFractalStage3Answer1">Okay, I will be back tomorrow with the results.</string>
	<string name="ObtainFractalStage5Answer0">So, the survey is complete and some kind of devilry is going on there. This time the length of the coast was 5.12 kilometers. How so?</string>
	<string name="ObtainFractalStage5Dialog0">That, my dear, is the paradox of the coastline. If you want to know more about it, ask the bobers, they are good not only at carpentry, but also at mathematics.</string>
	<string name="ObtainFractalStage5Answer1">That is what I will do.</string>
	<string name="ObtainFractalStage6Answer0">Hi, frogus said you could explain the coastline paradox to me.</string>
	<string name="ObtainFractalStage6Dialog0">Aaaah, paradoks linii brzegowej? Wiemy, wiemy. Mam o tym bardzo ciekawą książkę. Przeczytaj ją, jest w niej mnóstwo ciekawych rzeczy.</string>
	<string name="ObtainFractalStage6Answer1">Thank you very much, I think I will master it overnight.</string>
	<string name="MeditationStage1Answer0">Hey, my head is been buzzing with all sorts of thoughts lately. How do you always stay so rested?</string>
	<string name="MeditationStage1Dialog0">Ah, well, we Doguses have been learning meditation since childhood. Do you want me to teach you?</string>
	<string name="MeditationStage1Dialog1">To achieve enlightenment, do this:\n1. Get a Frogus - they know everything there is to know about meditation.\n2. As soon as it hatches, start practicing with it right away.\n3. Practice meditating with it every day.\n4. If you miss even one day, start over.\n5. Finishing 10 exercises will allow you to achieve enlightenment.</string>
	<string name="MeditationStage1Answer1">It sounds confusing, but I will try.</string>
	<string name="MeditationStage2Answer0">Hi, dogus said you can teach me meditation.</string>
	<string name="MeditationStage2Dialog0">Great, you have come to the right place. Let us start with something simple – breathing exercises. Repeat after me.</string>
	<string name="MeditationStage2Dialog1">Sorry, but you are a bit late, you need to find a younger Frogus.</string>
	<string name="MeditationStage2Dialog2">[Half an hour later] Well, that is great, come tomorrow, we will continue training.</string>
	<string name="MeditationStage3Answer0">Hi, I came to continue our training.</string>
	<string name="MeditationStage3Dialog0">You came too early, not even a day has passed since our last training, rest for now.</string>
	<string name="MeditationStage3Dialog1">Excellent! I see you are rested and ready to continue. Exercise for today is</string>
	<string name="MeditationStage3Dialog2">Unfortunately, you are more than two days late. That is not how things work. We will have to start all over again.</string>
	<string name="MeditationStage3Answer1">Oh, oh, what can you do...</string>
	<string name="MeditationStage3Dialog4">I have nothing more to teach you, child, you already know everything you need to know. From now on, you can free yourself from the thoughts that bother you at will. Congratulations!</string>
	<string name="MeditationStage3Answer2">Thank you for spending time with me! I have learned a lot.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage1Answer0">Hi, I have heard some disturbing rumors about the kingdom, do you know what they are all about?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage1Dialog0">The king was looking for you... but I was tasked with speaking. Time is running out, listen carefully. Last night, the necromancer Valherris infiltrated the royal preserve and stole what should have been guarded for centuries — a dragon egg. The necromancer intends to perform a ritual that will transform the dragon hatchling into a soulless creature. If he succeeds, the world awaits times far more terrible than any war. We have five days, no more.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage1Answer1">And what do you want from me?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage1Dialog1">You must assemble a party. Going there alone is certain death. But with the right pets… you have a chance.\n\nListen — you need four:\n- Dogus the warrior, whose strength is like a hammer on an anvil, and whose courage is stronger than steel. He will lead you through any enemy ranks.\n- Catus the mage — Well… that is me. And believe me, without my magic and knowledge of ancient runic paths, you will not get halfway.\n- Frogus the bard — his voice can calm the storm and dispel illusions. You need him not only as a musician — he knows paths hidden from maps.\n- Bober the blacksmith — he is a man of few words, but his hands can repair, destroy, or smelt almost anything. And without him, you will perish in the Ash Caves.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage1Answer2">Four different pets, yep, I get it.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage1Dialog2">Return to me when you have gathered them all. Go. Time is our enemy. Find them. Gather a squad. And return the egg... before the world turns to ashes.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage1Answer3">We will definitely cope!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage2Answer0">I want you to join our team to save the dragon egg.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage2Dialog0">Are you absolutely sure about this?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage2Answer1">Yes, I am sure you are the one we need!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage2Answer2">Wait, I need to think some more.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage2Dialog1">Okay, I will go collect everything I need.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage2Answer3">When you are ready, come to Catus mage, we will meet at his place.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage2Dialog2">Jestem zaszczycony takim zaufaniem! I will speak in a common language, it will be easier. Are you absolutely sure that I am the one you need?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage2Answer4">Everyone is assembled, we are ready to move out.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage2Dialog3">Very well, our first goal is to reach the Misty Gorge. The journey there will take about a day, so do not waste your energy, let us get going!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage2Answer5">Adventures await!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage3Answer0">Haven’t we reached the Misty Gorge yet?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage3Dialog0">Not yet, be patient.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage4Answer0">We’ve finally arrived, tell us what’s going on here.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage4Dialog0">We stand at the entrance to a gorge, shrouded in a thick silvery fog. Through it, distant whispers, footsteps, and strange laughter can be heard. The figures in the fog seem to be either human or monsters. I raise my staff, the crystal shimmers with an uncertain light.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage4Dialog1">Be careful. This is no ordinary fog. It’s saturated with the illusions of the ancient spirits of the gorge. It will distort distances, show false paths, make you see things that aren’t there... or things you’d rather not see at all. I sense that without the right approach, we could wander here for hours — or fall into traps.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage4Dialog2">Talk to everyone in the group. We all have our own ideas on how to best get through this place. You’ll have to choose the method that seems most suitable. When you’re ready, let me know your decision.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage5Answer0">How do you propose to get through the Misty Gorge?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage5Dialog0">I can dispel some of the spell. Not completely, but enough to reveal the true contours of the path. This is the safest path.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage5Dialog1">To hell with illusions! It’s all smoke and terror. I’ll lead the way, cutting a path with my sword. If there are phantoms, I’ll chop off their heads. If there are traps, I’ll withstand the blow. We’ll get to the end if we simply move forward, not letting the fog take over our minds.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage5Dialog2">The gorge sings. Do you hear it? These voices respond to the melody. If I find the right rhythm, I can keep us sane and prevent illusions from penetrating our hearts. We will follow my song — it will become the thread that will lead us out of this nightmare.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage5Dialog3">Illusions? Hm. We’re not afraid of them if we leave our mark. Look: if I drive iron pegs into the ground every twenty steps, we won’t get lost. And illusions... illusions don’t care where the iron is. The work is time-consuming, but reliable.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage5Answer1">I have heard all the options and am ready to decide what we will do.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage5Dialog4">Okay, so what did you decide?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage5Answer2">I agree with Catus’s proposal.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage5Answer3">I like Dogus’s idea</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage5Answer4">Frogus’s solution seems right.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage5Answer5">I have confidence in Bober’s approach.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage5Answer6">Actually, let me think a bit more...</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage5Dialog5">Okay, we trust your judgment. We’ll prepare and act according to the chosen plan. If we try, we’ll be done in an hour. Forward!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage7Answer0">How did we do?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage7Dialog0">We passed through the fog quickly and safely. At one point, I almost lost my concentration and one of the illusions almost distorted me, but I managed to pull through and led the group under a magical shield. We’re ready to continue our journey, our next destination is the Forest of Singing Winds, a journey that will take a day. Let’s go!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage7Dialog1">As expected, we quickly crossed the gorge. Dogus truly demonstrated his mastery of the sword, though it wasn’t particularly effective. One of the lurking illusions distorted half my face, but I noticed it in time and cast a spell to banish it. We’re ready to continue our journey, our next destination is the Forest of Singing Winds, a journey that will take a day. Let’s go!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage7Dialog2">I didn’t think Frogus’s plan would work, and I was surprised when the ghosts actually began to react to the rhythm of his melody. Not everyone reacted the same way, though — one of the lurking illusions distorted half my face, but I noticed it in time and cast a spell to banish it. We’re ready to continue our journey, our next destination is the Forest of Singing Winds, a journey that will take one day. Let’s go!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage7Dialog3">The Bober’s plan was indeed sound, albeit very slow. We fiddled around for so long that even the ghosts seemed to tire of it all and lost interest. I, too, soon lost interest, and in vain – one of the lurking illusions (which clearly hadn’t lost interest in us) distorted half my face, but I noticed it in time and banished it with a spell. We’re ready to continue on our way, our next destination is the Forest of Singing Winds, a day’s journey away. Onward!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage8Answer0">Haven’t we reached the Forest of Singing Winds yet?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage9Answer0">We’ve finally arrived, tell us what’s going on here.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage9Dialog0">We enter an ancient forest. The leaves tremble, though there’s barely a breath of wind. The air is filled with quiet yet eerie melodies — as if someone is singing from everywhere and nowhere at once. The voices grow louder, and the mood shifts strangely: now sudden joy, now melancholy, now a desire to stop and listen.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage9Dialog1">Wait... this is the Forest of Singing Winds. The ancient dryads cast a spell here to repel travelers. These voices affect the mind: they can lull you to sleep, lull you into oblivion, remind you of your most painful memories... We must pass quickly and resist their spell. Otherwise, they will lead us into the thicket, from which no one returns.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage9Dialog2">As before, talk to everyone in the group. We all have our own ideas on how to best get through this place. You’ll have to choose the method that seems most suitable. When you’re ready, let me know your decision.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage10Answer0">How do you propose to get through the Forest of Singing Winds?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage10Answer1">I have heard all the options and am ready to decide what we will do.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage10Dialog0">I can create a sound barrier, cutting off the dryads’ voices from our senses. A sphere of silence around us will allow us to pass more quickly. But it will require concentration... and if I weaken even for a moment, the spell might break through.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage10Dialog1">Spells, voices, songs… it’s all nonsense. If we just stick together and walk straight ahead, ignoring the voices, they won’t do anything to us. We plug our ears and move on. What could be so difficult?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage10Dialog2">Allow me. These melodies are no threat if you know how to respond. I can harmonize with the forest, align its voice with our steps. Then the dryads won’t touch us. I can’t promise the path will be easy... but we’ll remain sane.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage10Dialog3">Songs, whispers… they’re all empty sounds. If we create our own noise — loud, constant, rhythmic — the enemy’s melodies will lose their power. I can pound my hammer on my shield, setting the tempo. It will be unpleasant for everyone, but we will drown out their music.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage12Answer0">How did we do this time?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage12Dialog0">We walked slowly, adjusting to the rhythm of the forest. Frogus certainly knew his stuff — his melody harmonized so well with the forest’s song that, by the end, we heard the dryads’ pleas — they begged us to leave Frogus with them — they liked him so much. It’s a good thing we’d already passed the forest by this time. We are ready to move on, to the Stone Pass, the journey there would take a day. Onward!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage12Dialog1">My sound barrier worked, and we truly walked in complete silence. However, towards the end, Frogus admitted that his perfect pitch had indeed picked up the dryads’ melodies — they were asking him to stay with them. Now he’s acting out of sorts and muttering occasionally. Don’t worry, he’ll be fine. We’re ready to move on to Stone Pass, it’ll only take a day. Let’s go!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage12Dialog2">Dogus’s plan was as simple as he was — and it worked! I didn’t expect it, I didn’t expect it. However, in the end, Frogus admitted that his perfect pitch had indeed caught the dryads’ melodies — they were asking him to stay with them. Now he’s acting out of sorts and muttering occasionally. Don’t worry, he’ll be fine. We’re ready to move on to the Stone Pass, it’ll only take a day. Forward!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage12Dialog3">It seems Beaver has no understanding of music at all. It was miserable for everyone — us, the forest, and the dryads. In the end, Frogus admitted that his perfect pitch had finally caught the dryads’ melodies — they were asking him to stay with them. Now he’s acting out of sorts and muttering occasionally. Don’t worry, he’ll be fine. We’re ready to move on to Stone Pass, it’ll only take a day. Let’s go!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage13Answer0">Haven’t we reached the Stone Pass yet?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage14Answer0">We’ve finally arrived, tell us what’s going on here.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage14Dialog0">At dawn, we ascend a high-mountain trail. The narrow road passes beneath overhanging cliffs. A huge figure appears on the path — a giant of gray stone, as if carved from the mountain itself.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage14Dialog1">He holds a massive stone club and blocks the way, looking at us with motionless but attentive slit-like eyes.\n\n“Stop. This is my pass,” he says. “No one passes until they prove themselves worthy. Either by strength, or honor, or wisdom. Decide.”</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage14Dialog2">This giant is no simple creature. He is bound by an ancient pact with the mountains: to allow travelers through only after a trial. We must pass, otherwise we’ll have to find a way around… and that would be a waste of an entire day. We need to decide how to convince him. Return to me when you’re ready to make a decision.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage15Answer0">How do you propose to get through the Stone Pass?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage15Answer1">I have heard all the options and am ready to decide what we will do.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage15Dialog0">The giant’s skin is nearly impenetrable, but I have a spell that can blind him momentarily or create the illusion of a detour. We can get through while he’s disoriented. It’s dangerous… but possible.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage15Dialog1">It’s all perfectly clear. He wants a test, so I’ll give him one. I’ll challenge him to a fair fight, one-on-one. No magic, no tricks. If I can withstand his blow or force him to retreat, he’ll let us pass.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage15Dialog2">The giant is a great stone soul, let me turn to the ancient songs. I can soothe him, sing him a ballad of peace and freedom of the paths. Giants respect history and music — perhaps he will allow us to pass willingly, without a fight.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage15Dialog3">The giant is a stone. I am a blacksmith. We speak the same language. Allow me. I will offer to strengthen his club with my iron clamps. Improving the weapon is the best payment. Perhaps he will let us go for the work, without trials.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage17Answer0">How did we manage to defeat the giant?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage17Dialog0">Dogus challenged the giant to a fair duel. Despite the difference in height, our brave warrior was head and shoulders above his opponent in terms of weapon mastery. The giant soon conceded defeat and said he would long remember such a skilled warrior. We passed without delay. Well, it’s time to move on to the Ash Caves. Forward!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage17Dialog1">We barely had time to slip past the giant while he was blinded by my spell. Dogus, a true fighter, was displeased that he wasn’t allowed to challenge the giant to a duel, but the main thing is we slipped past without losses. Well, it’s time to head for the Ash Caves. Forward!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage17Dialog2">I don’t know whether Frogus made up these legends himself or read them somewhere, but it seems the giant truly enjoyed his stories. At the end, he sat motionless, pensively, gazing into the distance — we realized this was our chance to get through, and we took it. Dogus, however, was dissatisfied with not being allowed to challenge the giant to a duel, but the main thing is we slipped through without losses. Well, time to head for the Ash Caves. Forward!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage17Dialog3">I had no idea that Bober had brought along a whole arsenal of tools for upgrading and modernizing weapons in the field. The giant was also taken aback by the offer and, after some consideration, agreed. Bober did a splendid job. Dogus was displeased that he wasn’t allowed to challenge the giant to a duel, especially since, he said, giant now had a more powerful weapon than before! However, the main thing is that we got through without losses. Well, time to move on to the Ash Caves. Forward!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage18Answer0">Haven’t we reached the Ash Caves yet?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage19Answer0">We’ve finally arrived, tell us what’s going on here.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage19Dialog0">We descend into dark caves. The walls are covered in runes, and the ground vibrates beneath our feet. Deep below, the clatter of ancient machinery can be heard: the hiss of steam, the rumble of gears, the flashes of lava. Sharp gusts of hot air burst from the side pipes every now and then.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage19Dialog1">As soon as we take a few steps forward, one of the lattice doors slams behind us, forcing us to move only forward.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage19Dialog2">Be careful. These caves are the ancient workshops of the Ash Dwarves. Their technology combines mechanics and fiery runes. One mistake and we’ll end up under lava or trapped. But there’s no turning back. We must get through this scorching labyrinth. You know what to do.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage20Answer0">How do you propose to get through the Ash Caves?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage20Answer1">I have heard all the options and am ready to decide what we will do.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage20Dialog0">I have an idea. If we cool the air around us with ice magic, we can slow down some of the mechanisms. This will create a safe passageway. But fire and ice runes conflict… the consequences are unpredictable.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage20Dialog1">We’re wasting too much time. If we just move quickly, I can get through first and clear the way. Yes, it’s hot in some places, but we can’t stop. We’ll run where the furnaces are active and crawl where it’s too hot.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage20Dialog2">“The toothed wheels started spinning in my head.\nIn my wet head under the armor-piercing rain.”\n\nListen… these mechanisms work in rhythm. Can you hear it? “Knock-knock-shhhh” — repeating every few seconds. If we move to the rhythm, adjusting to the cycle, we can pass between the stoves and doors without coming into contact with the fire. The main thing is not to lose our rhythm.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage20Dialog3">This is my element. I know how these machines work. Give me time — I’ll check the pressure in the pipes, jam the dangerous gears, and shut down the unnecessary furnaces. If we follow me and do as I say, we’ll get through without any losses.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage22Answer0">How did we manage to get through fire, water and copper pipes?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage22Dialog0">We moved very slowly and carefully, Bober checking any suspicious levers and mechanisms with particular care. A couple of times we stumbled upon some red crystals growing out of the walls, which greatly intrigued Bober, but I hurried him on, reminding him that he was responsible for our safety. Overall, we made it out without any casualties. We’re almost there — it’s a day’s journey from here to the ritual site. Onward!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage22Dialog1">My plan worked, though it required extreme concentration on my part. Now everyone’s sniffling. In one of the corridors, some red crystals were growing out of the wall, which for some reason caught Bober’s interest. I didn’t have time to dwell on it, he seemed to have grabbed a couple of them, saying he’d study them in more detail later. We’re almost there — it’s a day’s journey from here to the ritual site. Let’s go!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage22Dialog2">Oh, that Dogus! He always thinks everyone around him is as tough as he is. Frogus and I nearly fell into a crevice trying to keep up with our brave warrior. In one of the corridors, some red crystals were growing out of the wall, which for some reason greatly interested Bober. We didn’t have time to dwell on them, he seemed to have grabbed a couple of them, saying he’d study them in more detail later. We’re almost there — it’s a day’s journey from here to the ritual site. Onward!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage22Dialog3">Well, that was quite an exercise in rhythm. I had no idea everyone in our group would be such natural dancers. We did lose our rhythm once because of Bober — some red crystals were growing out of the wall in one of the corridors, which for some reason caught his interest. We didn’t have time to dwell on it, but he seemed to have grabbed a couple of them, saying he’d study them in more detail later. We’re almost there — it’s a day’s journey from here to the ritual site. Onward!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage23Answer0">Haven’t we reached the ritual site yet?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage24Answer0">We are here, what is going on here?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage24Dialog0">We climb the shattered steps to the ritual chamber. The doors stand open, and an ominous green light pours from within. The air trembles with eerie whispers. In the center of the chamber stands a dragon’s egg, surrounded by runes. Valherris stands above it — tall, in tattered robes, his eyes as empty as night.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage24Dialog1">“It’s too late…” the necromancer says. “You’ve come too late. But if you want to die next to this damned egg, I don’t mind.”\nHe waves his hand, and hordes of minions burst from the shadows: skeleton knights, ghosts, shadows, and bone golems.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage24Dialog2">Valherris, you pathetic fool! Did you think I couldn’t recognize the spell of eternal summoning? You sold your soul in exchange for this final summoning, and your time is numbered! Now we can easily take the egg.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage24Dialog3">But there’s one problem… We’ll get the egg, but the minions will really be spawning forever. Whatever you say, that damn necromancer was incredibly powerful (now all that’s left of him is a robe on the floor). We don’t have much time, we can’t fight forever. One of us has to escape with the egg, and the others will buy him enough time. Decide, who among us will save the egg?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage24Answer1">It seems I have no other choice…</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage24Dialog7">But there’s one problem… We’ll get the egg, but the minions will really be spawning forever. Whatever you say, that damn necromancer was incredibly powerful (now all that’s left of him is a robe on the floor). We don’t have much time, we can’t fight forever. I never thought I’d have to resort to the power of the Necronomicon. It’s powerful enough for one of us to hold off the creatures long enough for the others to escape with the egg. Decide which of us will buy the others time?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Answer0">You will be the one who saves the egg…</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Answer1">I’m ready to make a choice…</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Dialog0">Who did you choose?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Answer2">I choose you, Catus…</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Answer3">I choose Dogus…</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Answer4">I choose Frogus…</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Answer5">I choose Bober…</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Dialog1">Are you absolutely sure?</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Answer6">Yes, I am sure.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Answer7">Let me think a bit more…</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Dialog2">Well, in that case, it’s time to say goodbye. I’m putting Dogus in charge of the team. Talk to him, and I have to go. There’s something I need to sort out…</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Answer8">Goodbye, my friend</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Answer9">Catus put you in charge, tell me what happened</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Dialog3">This is how it happened: Catus grabbed his staff, and a blue flame flared on it.\n\n— Necromancy raised these creatures. Magic will stop them. Go away.\n\nDrawing power from the cursed book, he creates a wall of energy that tears the air. The last thing you hear is his quiet voice:\n\n— It was an honor to walk with you.\n\nThe wall explodes with light, burying the mage and the hordes of the dead.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Dialog4">It’s time to go back, we don’t want his sacrifice to be in vain. The journey home will be easier and quicker, and it will only take one day. Let’s go!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Dialog6">Dogus places his cloak in your hands — he smiles for the first time in the entire adventure.\n\n— Take the egg. I will hold them back. Go.\n\nTouching the cursed book with his sword, he imbues it with mystical light. Turning, he charges into the ranks of the undead, shouting a battle cry that echoes throughout the hall…</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Dialog8">Frogus clutches the lyre to his chest. His eyes are sad, but confident.\n\n— We each have our own song, but the final one is always a solo. Remember me like this... singing.\n\nTouching the cursed book, he raises the lyre and plays a note that cracks the air. The melody cuts through the undead like a blade, and then everything around it. The song fades along with the bard’s life, opening the way for you.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Dialog10">Bober places his hand on your shoulder and looks at you calmly, as if this were all just another day’s work in the forge.\n\n— Iron bends under the hammer. And fate — under the choices we made. Go. I will bring down the halls behind me.\n\nHe waits until we run across the bridge, then, touching the cursed book, strikes the hammer against a supporting column. The entire temple begins to crumble. The last thing we see is Bober’s silhouette standing amidst the falling stones.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Dialog13">Dogus places his cloak in your hands — he smiles for the first time in the entire adventure. urning, he charges into the ranks of the undead, shouting a battle cry that echoes throughout the hall…</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Dialog14">Frogus clutches the lyre to his chest. His eyes are sad, but confident. He raises the lyre and plays a note that cracks the air. The melody cuts through the undead like a blade, and then everything around it. The song fades along with the bard’s life, opening the way</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Dialog15">Bober places his hand on your shoulder and looks at you calmly, as if this were all just another day’s work in the forge. He waits until we run across the bridge, then strikes the hammer against a supporting column. The entire temple begins to crumble. The last thing we see is Bober’s silhouette standing amidst the falling stones.</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Dialog16">It’s time to go back, we don’t want their sacrifice to be in vain. The journey home will be easier and quicker, and it will only take one day. Let’s go!</string>
	<string name="ObtainDragonStage25Dialog18">Catus grabs his staff, and a blue flame flares on it. He creates a wall of energy that tears the air. The wall explodes with light, burying the mage and the hordes of the dead.</string>

	<!-- Quest description -->
	<string name="QuestIsFinished">Done</string>
	<string name="QuestNameNecronomicon">Lost and found</string>
	<string name="QuestNameObtainFrogus">Fish and consequences</string>
	<string name="QuestNameObtainBober">Must be a wind</string>
	<string name="QuestNameObtainFractal">Coastline paradox</string>
	<string name="QuestNameMeditation">Mind games</string>
	<string name="QuestNameObtainDragon">Dragon age</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainFrogusStage0">Something tells me I need to make sure I understand the catus one hundred percent.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainFrogusStage1">Great, now I need to ask adult catus, maybe someone needs some help.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainFrogusStage2">As I thought, one of the katus asked me to diversify the menu and find some fish somewhere. I will look for it near the pond he was talking about.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainFrogusStage3">Well, I caught some fish, I should give it to the catus.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainFrogusStage4">Catus was pleased with my offering and said that he would go to the pond himself and evaluate its potential.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainFrogusStage5">I should probably ask Catus about his assessment of the pond.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainFrogusStage6">Well, the pond assessment turned out to be very successful, he even found a Frogus egg, which I am incredibly happy about.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescNecronomiconStage0">To begin with, it would be nice to fully understand dogus and catus. And wait for something wicked this way comes.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescNecronomiconStage1">Here comes another beautiful day.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescNecronomiconStage2">Nothing foreshadows trouble.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescNecronomiconStage3">Oh no! Someone dug up the grave without the consent of the deceased’s closest relatives! I need to ask around, maybe someone knows something.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescNecronomiconStage4">Dogus asked me to bring something from the grave so that he could begin his search.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescNecronomiconStage5">I found a piece of fabric, I need to show it to the dogus.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescNecronomiconStage6">Dogus said that he would try to follow the trail.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescNecronomiconStage7">I should ask the dogus if he found anything.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescNecronomiconStage8">I learned that catus are knowledgeable in magic. And the longer they live, the better they understand it. Perhaps one of them can help me with this mysterious book.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescNecronomiconStage9Use">The old catus told me that the book that dogus found was the Necronomicon. He also warned me that it was a very dangerous book. However, I decided to ignore him and wanted to learn the knowledge that this book contains. It seems that now I can resurrect the dead.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescNecronomiconStage9Destroy">The old katus told me that the book that the dogus found was the Necronomicon. He also warned me that it was a very dangerous book. Taking his advice, I decided to destroy the book. To be on the safe side.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainBoberStage0">To begin with, it would be nice to fully understand frogus and dogus.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainBoberStage1">The eggs are gone! The eggs are gone! What should I do?</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainBoberStage2">I will ask the pets, maybe they know something.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainBoberStage3">Dogus agreed to look for the eggs and said to give him a day to do it.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainBoberStage4">It seems it’s time to ask the dogus about the results of his search.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainBoberStage5">Dogus successfully returned the eggs to their place, now nothing will happen to them.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainBoberStage6">The eggs are gone again! What the hell is going on! Maybe someone else can help me?</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainBoberStage7">Dogus agreed to help me again and told me to think about solving the problem in the future.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainBoberStage8">Perhaps it’s time to ask the dogus about the search results again.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainBoberStage9">Dogus put all the eggs back in place. I really should ask the other pets to help me with this.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainBoberStage10">Frogus said that he would ask his friends from the pond, he said that they are handy and know their business.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainBoberStage11">It’s time to ask frogus if there is any news from his friends.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainBoberStage12">Wow! These Bober guys not only gave me a basket for eggs, but they also entrusted me with one of their eggs so that I could care for future generations of bobers.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainFractalStage0">To begin with, it would be nice to fully understand bober and frogus.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainFractalStage1">I have noticed that lately the froguses have been sitting in thought for a long time, I need to figure out what is going on.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainFractalStage2">Frogus asked me to measure the length of the pond shoreline using a two-meter stick. Why would he want that?</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainFractalStage3">Well, I have measured it, it is time to report the results.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainFractalStage4">Now frogus asked me to do the same thing, but with a different ruler.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainFractalStage5">This time I measured a completely different number. Strange, I will go ask frogus.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainFractalStage6">Frogus sent me to the bobers to find out about this paradox.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainFractalStage7">Bober gave me a book about mathematics, I will dive into it head first.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainFractalStage8">Wow, I learned a lot of new things there! What I liked most in this book were the fractals, now I know what they are and how different they are. I love imagining them!</string>
	<string name="QuestDescMeditationStage0">To begin with, it would be nice to fully understand frogus and dogus.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescMeditationStage1">My head is been spinning lately. I will ask the adult dogus how he always manages to stay so rested.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescMeditationStage2">Dogus told me to ask Frogus about meditation.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescMeditationStage3">We started intensive training with Frogus.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescMeditationStage4">I learned meditation practices and now I can forget anything I want!</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage0">To begin with, it would be nice to fully understand catus, frogus, dogus and bober.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage1">I heard some rumors about troubles in the kingdom, I think I will ask Catus about it.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage2">So, to save the egg I need to assemble a team of Catus, Dogus, Frogus and Bober.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage3">We set off for our first destination, Misty Gorge, which will take one day to get there.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage4">We have arrived at the Misty Gorge, how do we get through it?</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage5">I should ask the group how they propose to cross the Misty Gorge and choose the best option.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage6">I’ve made a decision on how to get through the Misty Gorge, and I hope it’s the right one.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage7">We’ve made it to the other side of the Misty Gorge, I need to find out from Catus about the team’s status.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage8">We are moving towards the next location - the Forest of Singing Winds.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage9">We have arrived at the Forest of Singing Winds, how do we get through it?</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage10">I should ask the group how they propose to cross the Forest of Singing Winds and choose the best option.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage11">I’ve made a decision on how to get through the Forest of Singing Winds, and I hope it’s the right one.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage12">We passed through the forest, I’ll ask Catus how successfully we did it.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage13">We move on - the Stone Pass awaits us.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage14">We have arrived at the Stone Pass, what danger awaits us here?</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage15">I should ask the group how they propose to cross the Stone Pass and choose the best option.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage16">I’ve made a decision on how to get through the Stone Pass, and I hope it’s the right one.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage17">It looks like we’ve overcome the giant, I’ll find out the details from Catus.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage18">We move on - the Ash Caves awaits us.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage19">We have arrived at the Ash Caves, what danger awaits us here?</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage20">I should ask the group how they propose to cross the Ash Caves and choose the best option.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage21">I’ve made a decision on how to get through the Ash Caves, and I hope it’s the right one.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage22">We got through the caves, I’ll ask Catus how we did.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage23">We’re almost there - to the ritual site!</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage24">We arrived at the site of the final battle.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage25YesNecro">The necromancer is defeated, but now I have to choose who will buy time for the others.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage25NoNecro">The necromancer is defeated, but now I must choose who will escape with the egg while the others hold off the creatures.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage26">We got the egg back, but at what cost! Time to go home.</string>
	<string name="QuestDescObtainDragonStage27">Here we are at home, time to honor the memory of the heroes and start hatching dragons!</string>
</resources>
